3h long live she looks
3h да здравствует она так смотрим друг
at each other like that and everyone who is the first cattle cleanliness
на друга и все кто первый скоты чистота
yes I am from Ukraine the city of Lenitsky and you are
да я из украины город леницкий а вы
from Russia but from the city of Sochi it is a very
откуда из россии но из города сочи очень
sunny city of Sochi
солнечный город сочи
you decided so family roulette to come
вы решили так семейная рулетка зайти
in the evening no we are not family and friends on
вечером нет мы не семейном и друзья по
friendly terms so  in the evening to go in and the water boils,
дружескими так вечером зайти и бурлит
it’s
вода
not just not interesting why there is behind the
не просто не интересно почему там за
hatch and whether it was caught
люка и навыбирали ли он попался
somehow in the summer, so I’m talking about politics about the
как-то летом вот я про политику про
war there, it’s just
войну там общаюсь с людьми то как раз
who specifically chooses Ukraine
кто специально украину выбирая 7
so I look
грамм злые что процесс и вот я смотрю
at how I’m asking people
как вот из людей я опрашиваю поддержит
whether they will support or support the war in Ukraine, so nine out of ten,
или войну в украине так девять из десяти
yes, they are too high, yes, there we have a genocide in the
да вот они и завышена да там у нас в
procession in Ukraine,
шествии украине геноцид фиксировать нас
then we need to meet the question of the Ukrainian to
тогда встречи на вопрос украинец
support and
поддерживать и
support, and you, of course, don’t support him in Ukraine
поддерживали а вы ему в украине конечно
there is russia attacked ukraine,
не то есть россия напала на украину таки
they can still support,
могут поддерживать
well, how would it happen what happened what
ну как бы случилось то что случилось что
do you think on this
вы думаете по этому
occasion the case of existing beings like
случаю случае существующей существ как
an asteroid fell no  who fell down, well,
астероид упал нет кого низвергся ну
something like this and Russia attacked Ukraine
примерно так и напала россия на украину
in this whole situation that you can
в этой все ситуация что вы можете у вас
have three points I
есть три пункта я
support I don’t support
поддерживаю не поддерживаю и
and we will support ours who
своей мы поддержим кого
your country
твою страну
Ukraine I need support we attacked
украина я поддержку нужен у нас напали
we are fighting and
мы боремся и
please tell me here I treat some god
скажите пожалуйста вот я некоторым богом
lived in the Donbass for many years, Donetsk was
несколько много лет прожил на донбассе
ordered for
велено
14 years, for example, here’s mine, I didn’t fight, didn’t
14 года например вот моя я не воевал не
[ __ ], didn’t do anything,
низ трахался не ничего не делал
my apartment, my house was distributed by the
мою квартиру мой дом раздал била
Ukrainian artillery, this is a fact, it’s
украинская артиллерия это факт возможно
possible that
так и
I lost my job, judging by my nickname, I
я потерял работу об судя по нику я
lost my family,
потерял семью
please tell me here
скажите пожалуйста вот
how, like
как как
Ukrainians, like the Ukrainian people, just about I
украинцы как украинский народ вот-вот я
didn’t try, I shot, let me already
ни старался я настрелял давайте я уже
answer on the pass what should I do,
могу ответить по перевалу что мне делать
but don’t let us first figure
но не давайте мы сначала разберемся
out why it happened who started the
из-за чего это получилось кто начал
war, you, as a person, you lived in
войну вот вы как человек вы жили в
Donetsk, so you can  to say when
донецке так вот можете сказать когда
the hostilities began on the territory of the
начались боевые действия на территории
Donetsk region I can say the
донецкой области я могу сказать
hostilities on the territory of the Donetsk
боевые действия на территории донецкой
region began that  to marriage when the Maidan began,
области начались так брак когда начался
you can tell the date
майдан дату можете сказать дату когда
when in Donetsk there tanks fired something
вот в донецке там танки стреляли что-то
on Slavic planes
самолетах славянский
on April 12 to be absolutely right, let's
12 апреля чтобы абсолютно верно давайте
do this until April 12, 14 there were some kind of
так до 12 апреля 14 года были какие-то
hostilities in Donetsk, I didn’t
боевые действия у вас донецке мне не
have it, but because I  Russian hashish,
было так а потому что мне русские гашиш
it wasn’t, that is, it turns out
это были не было то есть получается до
before this Girkin came from Russia with
того как вот этот гиркин так из россии с
militants, captured Slavyansk, and
боевиками пришел захватил славянск а и
an anti-terrorist operation began
началась антитеррористическая операция
from this, no one killed anyone, not a
из этого никто никого не убивал ни
single killed wounded,
одного убитого раненого
they started killing on the Maidan on February the
убивать начали еще на майдане феврале
fourteenth again let's do it
четырнадцатого еще раз давайте так
we are dismantling on the Maidan so
давайте мы разбираем на майдане так
no one there is creaking there,
никого там издание скрипящими там
doubled on the contrary, people who
удвоенный наоборот людей которые за
killed the golden eagle there for the Maidan and
беркут убивал там а
who did not kill the local salt, let
кто убивал не местный соль давайте
's look at the Donbass here on April
разберемся про донбасс вот 12 апреля до
12 until April 12, these were at least one killed,
12 апреля эти был хоть один убитый так
for example, some troops should be in
например войсками какими-то надо в
Donetsk and  Luhansk region name it
донецкой и луганской области назови нее
was not there is absolutely right, that is, it
не было нет абсолютно верно то есть
turns out before the arrival of Russian
получается до прихода российских
militants girkin  and when they wanted
боевиков гиркина когда они захотели
Slavyansk, they seized the police departments with
славянска захватили отделений полиции с
grenade launchers, two days later they seized the
гранатометами через два дня захватили
throat in the throat, they killed the deputy of the
горловку в горловке убили депутата
city council, Vladimir Rybak, the
городского совета владимира рыбака на
next day after the capture, because
следующий день после захвата потому что
he hung the Ukrainian flag back
он повесил назад украинский флаг
, terrorists came from another country, they
пришли террористы из другой страны
seized
захватили
the law enforcement agencies, how they started people to the
органы правопорядка как начали людей на
basement was in  in Slavyansk they sat in the basement of
подвал был в славянске сидели на подвал
people as they planted, yes, that is, it turns out
людей как садили да то есть получается
shooters and a company of everyone who does not agree
стрелков и компания всех кто не согласны
either killed or threw
либо убивали либо кидали
distortions if they killed it for a sensible basement,
передергивания если за дельные подвал
let's
это убивали это это давайте на то что
go to the basement.  that is, they were illegally
сходили на подвал . то есть незаконно
detained, yes, it turns out the key to be
задерживали да получается key to be
before these Russian
до того как вот эти русские вы боевики
militants entered the territory of the Donbass and did not
не зашли на территорию донбасса и не
begin to seize any
начали захватывать никаких боевых
hostilities.
пожалуйста кто виноват в том что в мой
the house went to the dvina
дом пошли двины
directly my house who is to blame
непосредственно мой дом кто виноват
let's go so who started the war the
давайте так кто начал войну
war started long before us the first one
войну начали задолго до нас первый еще
again can fight again so the
раз еще раз может драться так боевые
fighting in the donbas ukraine did not start
действия на донбассе украина не начинала
you talk practically I talk
вы рассуждаете практически я рассуждаю
strategically let's take the
стратегически давайте по фактам
facts long before Kirkin because of the long  once
нас задолго до киркина из-за долго еще
again, if they started as specifically who died
раз если начали как конкретно погибший
in this war, so where are the military
на этой войне так где кого там боевые
battles that were in this war before
сражения какие были на этой войне до 12
April 12,
апреля
no, again, the point is that I'm not like that, I
еще раз дело в том что я не
worked for one of the gay
14 года работал на одну из гейских
publications from Donetsk in February 14 to
изданий из донецка
call the publication what
называть издание что
are you
вы очень
I hope very loyally as the official government, and
лояльно надеюсь как официальная власть и
well, I’ll say this to the rebels in Donetsk,
ну скажу так повстанцам в донецке
they tried very hard
очень старались
which month you say the
какой месяц говорите
keys and  there were no rebels who didn’t
ключи и виляющие никаких повстанцев не
have any rebels in February it’s
было какой какие повстанцы феврале
even a pity that I turned off I love these
даже жалко что отключился я обожаю эти
conversations with just grandchildren and the LC DPR
разговоры с просто внукам и лнр днр так
so people in and to
что люди на и к
Donetsk so
донецка так
hail flew into my apartment so I
китая в мою квартиру прилетел град так я
was left without an apartment I lost my job
остался без квартиры я потерял работу
went to another country in
уехал в другую страну в россию
Russian specialty nuts are in Russian on the nose,
орехи специальности же по-русски на носу
but the Russians who listen also understood the
же россияне которые слушают тоже поняли
person does not understand the
человек не понимает
causal relationship, because of which
причинно-следственной связи из-за чего
his house began to weave, then this is not just
его дом начала плели то это ж не просто
Ukraine, but there he is also a dude
украина а там чувак он тоже 2 и бахнуть
on April 17, Russian militants began to
17 апреля российские боевики начали
seize  cities of ukraine, this man
захват городов украины этот человек
absolutely understands this, he admits it, he
абсолютно это понимает он это признаю он
saw it all with his own eyes,
это видел все своими глазами
or that they killed it, that they detained it,
или то что убивали это что задерживали
they
там
scoffed at the basement and threw it
издевались на подвал и бросали так
there, so many have been sitting there for years,
многие там годами сидели там
thermal insulation in Donetsk, until now,
термоизоляция в донецке до сих пор
this is
это
from before these Russian
от до того как эти российские
military men found  ukraine no one black no
военные нашли украину никто черный никто
one was killed no one was fired
не был убит никто не был обстрелян
on  these militants did not come and
если бы эти люди боевики не пришли и
seized
захватили
the law enforcement agencies
органы правопорядка
there would be no anti-terrorist
не было бы никакой антитеррористической
operation that against these same people
операции которые против этих же людей
there were armed
было вооруженных
foreigners
иностран
yes there was a local klim they
да был местный клим
also pulled up weapons and handed out
подтягивали тоже оружием и раздавали
there you can climb all sorts of Cossacks and
там можно полезла всякая и казачество и
from Russia and apostates they are not there and
из россии и отступники их там нет и
Russian military
российские военные
people  does not understand that these people
человек не понимает что эти люди
or Russia
или россию
fired at Ukrainian positions,
обстреливали украинские позиции
naturally that Ukraine fired at
естественно что украина обстреливал
their positions,
ихние позиции
he absolutely knows that they were in the
он абсолютно знает что они же находились
cities, they are hot
городах это они горячо
there, the basics are hiding in the cities, all the
там азов прячется в города все
armies sitting in the cities, the soul is a natural
армии сидя в городах душа это природное
barrier,
заслон
and these militants did not sit
и вот эти боевики не сидели
re
ре
he did not  condemns them, they
он не осуждает их
went and captured parts of you country,
шли захватили части вы страны
he says that I must 9 because
он говорит что я должен 9 потому что
a gram rocket arrived,
прилетела ракета
so if Hitler attacked the Soviet
грамм так если гитлер напал на советский
Union,
союз
I of the Soviet Union, the Soviet Red
я советского союза советская красная
Army liberated the cities to the
армия освобождала города
Nazis, and those who captured
фашистам а которые захватили
were at the same time destroying you, but she
были при этом разрушению вы но она
liberated because these went to get up
освобождал потому что пошли встают эти
so the nazis they took over put
так нацистах они захватили put
takeover  these militants were Russian
захватчиками были российские эти боевики
and it is
и
natural that the state came to
естественно что государство дошло
restore order on its territory
восстановить порядок на своей территории
instead of letting these militants
вместо того чтобы давать этим боевикам
rape, kill and
насиловать убивать и
somehow teach other people from the Russians to the cat from the
как-то коту от русские
DPR with the LPR I really need
с с людьми из днр с лнр очень надо
to say I love this moment they are like
говорить я люблю этот момент они как
no one else  the Russians heard from fairy tales they
никто россияне с по сказкам слышали они
saw it all
видели вот это все
was until the 12th there was nothing so the
было до 12-го числа не было так ничего
militants started to kill it is necessary and the tractor
начали боевики убивать надо и тягач
we subscribe like it
подписываемся ставим лайк
in the comments and
в комментарях и
rome and informatively to me yes a thousand to
рим и информативно моему да штука тыс до
every Ukrainian is similar to Ukraine the price of a
каждого украинца похож на украине цена у
kupava on them  territories of the food of the skin
купава на их территориях еду кожного
thief,
вора
he is still, that is, betrayed by our side,
он еще то есть предана нашу сторону
that is, the son
а то есть сына
from Ukraine
со украине